[
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99D_MSQ_01_RescueWarden",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99D_MSQ_01_RescueWarden_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99D_Yonas_A",
		"AchievementId": "99D_MSQ_01",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_12||(99_MSQ_35&&!99_MSQ_56)",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99D_MSQ_01_RescueWarden_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "earringgreatcleavet5",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99D_MSQ_01_RescueWarden_title",
		"Description": "@99D_MSQ_01_RescueWarden_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99D_MSQ_01_RescueWarden_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99D_MSQ_01_RescueWarden_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99D_MSQ_01_RescueWarden_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99D_MSQ_01_RescueWarden_completion_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99D_MSQ_02_ClimbRuins",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99D_MSQ_02_ClimbRuins_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99D_Galahad_C",
		"AchievementId": "99D_MSQ_02",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99D_MSQ_01",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99D_MSQ_02_ClimbRuins_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT4_Headgear_40",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99D_MSQ_02_ClimbRuins_title",
		"Description": "@99D_MSQ_02_ClimbRuins_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99D_MSQ_02_ClimbRuins_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99D_MSQ_02_ClimbRuins_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99D_MSQ_02_ClimbRuins_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99D_MSQ_02_ClimbRuins_completion_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99D_MSQ_03_ThorpeBackstory",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99D_MSQ_03_ThorpeBackstory_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99D_Yonas_B",
		"AchievementId": "99D_MSQ_03",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99D_MSQ_02",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99D_MSQ_03_ThorpeBackstory_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT4_Footwear_40",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99D_MSQ_03_ThorpeBackstory_title",
		"Description": "@99D_MSQ_03_ThorpeBackstory_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99D_MSQ_03_ThorpeBackstory_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99D_MSQ_03_ThorpeBackstory_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99D_MSQ_03_ThorpeBackstory_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99D_MSQ_03_ThorpeBackstory_completion_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99D_MSQ_04_DestroyMines",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99D_MSQ_04_DestroyMines_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99D_Yonas_C",
		"AchievementId": "99D_MSQ_04",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99D_MSQ_03",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99D_MSQ_04_DestroyMines_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT4_Weapons_40",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99D_MSQ_04_DestroyMines_title",
		"Description": "@99D_MSQ_04_DestroyMines_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99D_MSQ_04_DestroyMines_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99D_MSQ_04_DestroyMines_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99D_MSQ_04_DestroyMines_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99D_MSQ_04_DestroyMines_completion_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99D_MSQ_05_CrossBridge",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99D_MSQ_05_CrossBridge_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99D_Galahad_E",
		"AchievementId": "99D_MSQ_05",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99D_MSQ_04",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99D_MSQ_05_CrossBridge_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT4_Handwear_45",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99D_MSQ_05_CrossBridge_title",
		"Description": "@99D_MSQ_05_CrossBridge_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99D_MSQ_05_CrossBridge_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99D_MSQ_05_CrossBridge_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99D_MSQ_05_CrossBridge_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99D_MSQ_05_CrossBridge_completion_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99D_MSQ_06_DestroyPortals",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99D_MSQ_06_DestroyPortals_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99D_Yonas_D",
		"AchievementId": "99D_MSQ_06",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99D_MSQ_05",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99D_MSQ_06_DestroyPortals_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionHealthT4",
		"ItemRewardQty": 10,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99D_MSQ_06_DestroyPortals_title",
		"Description": "@99D_MSQ_06_DestroyPortals_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99D_MSQ_06_DestroyPortals_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99D_MSQ_06_DestroyPortals_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99D_MSQ_06_DestroyPortals_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99D_MSQ_06_DestroyPortals_completion_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99D_MSQ_07_PortalFight",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99D_MSQ_07_PortalFight_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99D_Yonas_F",
		"AchievementId": "99D_MSQ_07",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99D_MSQ_06",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99D_MSQ_07_PortalFight_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT4_Chestwear_45",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99D_MSQ_07_PortalFight_title",
		"Description": "@99D_MSQ_07_PortalFight_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99D_MSQ_07_PortalFight_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99D_MSQ_07_PortalFight_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99D_MSQ_07_PortalFight_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99D_MSQ_07_PortalFight_completion_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"NOTE": "Soul Trial"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99D_MSQ_08_ThorpeFight",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99D_MSQ_08_ThorpeFight_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99D_Yash_F",
		"AchievementId": "99D_MSQ_08",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99D_MSQ_07",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99D_MSQ_08_ThorpeFight_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "HoningStoneT4",
		"ItemRewardQty": 3,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99D_MSQ_08_ThorpeFight_title",
		"Description": "@99D_MSQ_08_ThorpeFight_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99D_MSQ_08_ThorpeFight_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99D_MSQ_08_ThorpeFight_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99D_MSQ_08_ThorpeFight_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99D_MSQ_08_ThorpeFight_completion_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99D_MSQ_09_Outpost",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99D_Grace",
		"AchievementId": "99D_MSQ_09",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99D_MSQ_08 && !Archetype_Mercenary && !Archetype_Warmonger && !Archetype_Tracker && !Archetype_Musketeer && !Archetype_Occultist && !Archetype_Theurgist && !Archetype_Wanderer",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT4_Legwear_50",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_title",
		"Description": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_completion_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_destroyer",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99D_Grace",
		"AchievementId": "99D_MSQ_09",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99D_MSQ_08 && Archetype_Warmonger",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_success_destroyer",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT4_Legwear_50",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_title",
		"Description": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_completion_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_musketeer",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99D_Grace",
		"AchievementId": "99D_MSQ_09",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99D_MSQ_08 && Archetype_Musketeer",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_success_musketeer",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT4_Legwear_50",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_title",
		"Description": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_completion_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_mystic",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99D_Grace",
		"AchievementId": "99D_MSQ_09",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99D_MSQ_08 && Archetype_Theurgist",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_success_mystic",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT4_Legwear_50",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_title",
		"Description": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_completion_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_occultist",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99D_Grace",
		"AchievementId": "99D_MSQ_09",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99D_MSQ_08 && Archetype_Occultist",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_success_occultist",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT4_Legwear_50",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_title",
		"Description": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_completion_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_ranger",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99D_Grace",
		"AchievementId": "99D_MSQ_09",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99D_MSQ_08 && Archetype_Tracker",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_success_ranger",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT4_Legwear_50",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_title",
		"Description": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_completion_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_soldier",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99D_Grace",
		"AchievementId": "99D_MSQ_09",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99D_MSQ_08 && Archetype_Mercenary",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_success_soldier",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT4_Legwear_50",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_title",
		"Description": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_completion_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_swordsman",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99D_Grace",
		"AchievementId": "99D_MSQ_09",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99D_MSQ_08 && Archetype_Wanderer",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_success_swordsman",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT4_Legwear_50",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_title",
		"Description": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_completion_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99D_MSQ_10_CaerDun",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99D_MSQ_10_CaerDun_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99E_Sun_p1",
		"AchievementId": "99D_MSQ_10",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99D_MSQ_09",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99D_MSQ_10_CaerDun_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionHealthT4",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99D_MSQ_10_CaerDun_title",
		"Description": "@99D_MSQ_10_CaerDun_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99D_MSQ_10_CaerDun_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99D_MSQ_10_CaerDun_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99D_MSQ_10_CaerDun_incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99D_MSQ_10_CaerDun_completion_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	}
]